const data=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'qewewqqew werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:'asddsd sdadasdwerree dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'adddadas werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:'werweerwerrew sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'fgddgfdgfdfgd werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd werrewreerw asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'hjgjhghjg werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas weryrty tryytrty wwer?',
        answer:'ghjhgjhj werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:'gfgfgfhgfgghf sdadasd dsadds dfgfdg aaddsds?',
        answer:'uiooiiooiuio werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'ewrerewerrwe werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'qewewqqew werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:'asddsd sdadasdwerree dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'adddadas werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:'werweerwerrew sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'fgddgfdgfdfgd werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:11,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd werrewreerw asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'hjgjhghjg werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:12,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas weryrty tryytrty wwer?',
        answer:'ghjhgjhj werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:13,
        question:'gfgfgfhgfgghf sdadasd dsadds dfgfdg aaddsds?',
        answer:'uiooiiooiuio werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
    {
        id:14,
        question:'asddsd sdadasd dsadds asdsdas aaddsds?',
        answer:'ewrerewerrwe werweerrewr rewrwererwe rewreerwer wererwereerw wererwerer wererwerwer erwerwerwer erwerwererw ewrerwerwerw'
    },
]
export default data;